epicpoker.com 2012-07-11

# Privacy Policy - Epic Poker

_Last updated on July 25, 2011  
_  
Federated Sports and Gaming, Inc. (“FSG”) respects the privacy of its customers and users. This notice describes FSG’s privacy policy as it pertains to the Epic Poker website located at [http://www.epicpoker.com](http://www.epicpoker.com/) (the "Website"). We may, from time to time, revise this privacy policy, and the date of last revision will be available at the top of this page, so please be sure to check back periodically. **By using the Website, you are acknowledging and accepting this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after changes have been posted to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.**

What information we collect: FSG collects your e-mail address if you communicate with us by e-mail, as well as other personal information that you might supply voluntarily. FSG may also collect information about the actions you take on the Website. 

**How FSG uses your information:** FSG may use your information for the following purposes:

  • To respond to e-mails, inquiries or requests.   
• To enable you to post comments or submit other content to the Website.   
• To notify you about information regarding Federated Sports and Gaming or the Website that may be of interest to you.   
• To enable you to receive personalized content.   
• For the purposes for which you provided the information.   
• To improve the content and navigability of the Website.   
• To alert you to new Website features, special events, products and services.   
• For marketing and promotional purposes.   
• To customize the advertising and content you see, including the display of targeted advertisements.   
• To generate anonymous and/or aggregated reporting.   
• To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Website. 

Persons who assist FSG in providing the functions described in the previous section, including outside consultants, independent contractors, and third parties, may have authorized access to your personal information. 

We may use personal information we collect to create anonymous and/or aggregated data, and we may also combine personal information with other information for this purpose. FSG reserves the right to create, use, and disclose anonymous and/or aggregated data for any reason, without limitation, and such data is not subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

In the future, we may sell some or all of our assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event of a sale of our assets including our database, customer information will be transferred. 

**Who we share the information with:** FSG may, from time to time, share your personal information with affiliates and partners to enable you to receive information about products and services we think may interest you. We also may disclose your personal information to others when we have your consent to do so, or when we respond to a subpoena, legal order or official request, or when we believe you have acted in violation of the legal terms that govern your use of the Website. 

**Other Data Collection:** In addition to the information you knowingly provide, FSG may collect the domains and IP addresses of its visitors. We also may collect usage statistics such as web browser types and page requests. This data is used to more efficiently operate and administer the Website and promote our product and services. 

**Cookies:** "Cookies" are small elements of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. For example, some pages on our Website may use cookies so that FSG can provide you easier access to registered user areas, or track your preferences to improve your Website experience. Depending on your browser type, you can probably set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. However, please note that disabling cookies may prevent you from taking advantage of certain features on the Website. 

FSG may allow ad networks, such as third party ad servers and ad agencies, to serve advertisements within our web pages. We may also place web beacons for these companies within our pages. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. 

How we protect information: FSG attempts to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information. Our servers are protected by reasonable physical and electronic security measures. 

**Children Under 13:** The Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. FSG does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. 

**Links:** The Website may contain links to third-party websites. FSG is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

**Your California Privacy Rights:** Individual users who reside in California and have provided personal information to Federated Sports and Gaming may request information about our disclosures of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please submit a written request to 1740 N. St. NW, Washington DC 20036, Attention: Your California Privacy Rights. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. Please allow thirty (30) days for response. We reserve the right not to respond to requests submitted in any way other than as specified in this paragraph. 

**Contact Us:** If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at [info@federatedinc.com](mailto:info@federatedinc.com).
